Guide to the Affirmative Action Office Records 1971-2010
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections & Archives Research Center
- Reports, 1976-1998; Series IV
  - Funding Assistive Technology Devices: A Resource Manual for Oregon, 1990 (Box 9)
  - Keeping Our Faculties: Addressing the Recruitment and Retention of Faculty of Color in Higher Education, 1998 (Box 9)
    Conference presentation outline from Stephanie Sanford.
  - Making the Case for Affirmative Action in Higher Education: A Handbook for Organizers, Fall, 1995 (Box 9)
    Report by the American Council on Education.
  - Athletic Conciliation Report, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Response of OSU to ACLU Complaint of Sex Discrimination in Athletics, 1980 (Box 9)
  - Status of Minority Faculty Recruitment and Retention and Perceptions of the Campus Climate by Minority Faculty, August, 1994 (Box 9)
    Report by the Minority Affairs Commission.
  - Title IX Interim Report, 1976; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Unit Level Plans to Advance the AIMS, 1995 (Box 9)
  - Working with Differences in Communities, circa 1998 (Box 9)
    Report by OSU Extension.
  - Minority Report on OSU Affirmative Action Document of February 3rd, 1972 (Box 9)
    Minority report prepared by the Oregon State University Women's Study Group and submitted to Marlaina Kiner, Director of the Office for Civil Rights, on February 24, 1972.
- Publications, 1977-2010; Series V
  Series V consists of publications prepared and distributed by the Affirmative Action Office and includes brochures, newsletters, and directories. The newsletters, Current Comments (1977-1978) and Affirmative Action News (1986-1990), include information about staff, events, and programs. The Resource Directory was prepared as a tool to assist OSU offices and department in recruiting and employing members of under-represented groups. The series also includes a booklet for recruitment of minority graduate students.
  - Newsletter, 1977-1990 (Box 9)
  - Resource Directory, 1977-1996; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Advertising and Recruiting Resources, circa 1998 (Box 9)
  - Making OSU Your Next Step: Graduate Opportunities for Minorities, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Brochures, 1984-2010 (Box 9)